I have two public campers and I'm scared to go to prison by the 90th birthday of the year.
I'm going to go back to work and I'm going to go back to work and I'm going to go back to work.
I'm going to work for Joseph.
I'm from Tenning Grant, a potential towards humans.
I'm from Tenning Grant, a provincial phoenix and we've been very, very, very, very, very proud of the system.
The cloud has to be in the cloud.
We want to go to the barn and say the very, very straightened families and the things they want to take care of for the police.
So we'd be very, very, very honored.
So these are our four persons of property that will put up a lawsuit that will put them in the ground.
that the whole avid G-R-E-A settled with the rich G-R-E-A.
And such, as I said, has become one of these partions.
One of the settlement of those lawsuits that we've been connecting,
but the owners would be thanking the reason,
that floor agency is the T-G-R-E-R-E-R university.
The properties which, of course, is what we've been on in the whole of Orleans.
but I need to follow these months and so this simply completes that portion of those, those transactions.
It's not only putting the bottom of the course beyond the property but nothing could ever be done with the property, but it's not a front line.
So, by granting the phologites and since it's still worth an argument, the GR&E should be doing for a lot of other properties as well.
I mean, didn't you have to mean this for the front line?
It's part of the settlement.
That's correct.
In fact, we probably have more of these kind of more of these lawsuits or even seven-wire attorneys.
So, it wouldn't be surprising to me that Steve Mons still won't have a certain more of these than we've done before.
You know what I mean?
Hmm.
You just don't mind the more to go for a second.
Jonathan?
Uh, four steps.
Uh, what's that?
What's that?
I don't know.
So, that's four.
I don't know if it's one or two.
It's one or three.
I don't know.
So, that's the one.
What's he doing with that?
I am.
Take a minute.
Well, I'm not going to throw you any good balls, but I just have one thing.
It's important to be able to speak behind it.
Today, the way our ordinances are listening as to when our offices will be closed
over the Christmas holiday.
We decided that since we're closed on the Christmas Eve and Christmas Day,
and since Christmas Eve falls on its Sunday,
it's always the day after the Sunday that the holiday falls,
which would mean our Christmas Eve holiday will fall on Christmas Day.
So we're intending to have a holiday before the holiday,
which will be the weekend, which will be the 2034.
And then the two holidays, meaning that the civic Sunday will be closed,
will be the 25th and the 26th of the year.
That would be my main Tuesday for that.
Now, I think just from holiday planning standpoint,
I don't think it's either being kind of a problem with my son,
my operation is simply, and it probably will be a lot better for most employees.
We would normally have a study session scheduled when it sets.
I'm not anticipating the alarm at close after Christmas.
And usually the last meeting in December,
and we take a hard look at it and decide whether or not we need to realize
that we need to be somewhere in a different way.
But if that holds true, after this meeting, we don't even have about four minutes.
About three, no, see the four more meetings regularly,
as well, and this year.
And sitting here before the meeting, talking to Ben,
we're going to be bringing a lot of bewordsments to this,
like the animal ordinance, some of the other policies,
and things such as that, probably before the end of the year.
So, enjoy these short meetings, because we may not be able to be happy with it.
So, all that lies on here.
Well, we'll blame it on reading, we'll blame it on Ben.
But that's the reason we had our study sessions telling you all the things
that are coming up.
So, I just kind of wanted to give you a little foreshadowing.
You just kind of also just a realization of how quickly 27 teams
are going to be getting away from us.
So, you're anticipating the 7 or 4 from the 8th of July,
but I'm not scared of the 5th and 9th.
And the 7th of July will be our long-term meeting.
It would be our long-term meeting.
It would be our long-term meetings, and I said,
exactly, we have usually either avoiding the meeting,
a second meeting in December or half of just a very short meeting,
take care of reaching this.
So, just something to keep in mind is we blame our countries.
Yeah.
And really, that's it for me.
Well, I should be going to have,
and I should be on the 30th of October,
and I'm going to have to ask it.
And to a great degree, we're just kind of closest people on the calendar.
Yeah, I don't know what we did.
Yeah.
So, we don't have to make that decision today, but I guess more of that.
Let you know we're going to have to do that in the not too busy